Hello Sasikumar,
you can watch the job description of Tax Sales Executive in this video.  So, if you want to
become a sales executive, you'll
need all the things for your job.  Come and see it in this video
.  Sales Executive Job
Description A sales executive is a
person who does the sales for the
product and service of a business.
Products and services are
sold to our business. So that is
the work for the sales person.
Now this sales person, that
sales executive, his job is
very simple. You can come to a
bakery and design it for yourself
.  What does a salesman do in a bakery? When a
customer
comes in and asks him to buy a product, he initiates the conversation and
then explains the product and
then negotiates.
This is what they do. They come and give
a simple description of a sales executive.
We still have to come and
tell them in detail. If we want to break down a sales
executive job description into three simple descriptions, then we can say
that in a simple way.
Engage and excel. He engages with the customer and
explains the product.
2. Negotiating
and closing the deal. He negotiates and
closes the deal. 3. He negotiates with the customer.
Throughflows and Relationships They buy a customer and go away without leaving him, they
come back to him, follow up with that
customer, follow up with him, talk to him and
maintain those relationships. So I
told you these three things, didn't they?
Engage and Explain Negotiate and
Close the Deal and Retain the Customer
Throughflows and Relationships These are the characteristics of
these three main characteristics. If
you had known this in your job description, you would not have come to the
job of a sales executive saying, "You are a sales executive, now these customers are coming."
Most of the time, it will have the value of a
marketing person
or a lead generation expert
.  What these
marketing experts, lead generation
experts, will do is send potential
customers to the sales team
.  Please send it to the sales person
.  The sales person will
handle them.  Sales people
directly come and handle customers, so
they come and help them generate revenue, so they are the crucial part of the business. Sales is a
crucial part of the business. Sales
people, these sales executives,
directly
support the development of the business.  After this sales part
is over, it
will go to customer support.  So this
sales process is
an important
team that comes between the marketing process, that is, the lead generation process, and the customer support process, and handles customers directly. This sales team is a job.
This sales job is a job.
Now let's tell you a scenario. There
were two sales people in a bakery.
Only one sales person is doing well, and
another person comes and does a little poorly. Same scenario, same atmosphere,
but if you see how only one sales person
exits from this, there are
some things that come to that person who did good sales and made this exit
.  If you come and
see one, why does he come to these sales and
get a pass? Then you
can take that pass.  If you
come and see PASS, you will see that they
give their customers a personal touch, a personal approach.  The second is anticipating the needs of the customer
by providing special service to those customers.
How can we do all this?
You must have already seen a lot of customers who come regularly. We analyze our history of customers who come to that store frequently and who come to that business frequently.
You can achieve all of this when you make better use of the experience you've built with those customers
.  So, all of this is an
important
job description for a sales executive.  Reach out
to customers and engage them.
Products should be well explained and
the product knowledge
and service should be
communicated well. You should have that feeling of assisting the customers.
You should have that skill
of assisting the customers.
Fashions are very important.  So all this
comes from this skill slam and you will definitely be the best
sales executive. This is the
most important job
description for a sales executive. Apart from this,
companies will add many descriptions.
Some people will take pressure. Some
people will take experience. They will come and add
some additional
things to their job description. Thank you very much.
This is
Sasikumar Docs.